【The fate that cannot be liberated】
【无法解脱的命运】
[Episode 4]
[第4集]
I'm here to discuss with His Majesty
我是来跟陛下商量的
The alliance between Xunnan and Jialin.
寻南与嘉琳的联盟。
If I married a Jialin woman
如果我娶了一个嘉林的女人
Our alliance will be more stable.
我们的联盟将会更加稳定。
It turned out to be my senior.
原来是我的前辈。
I think Miss He is the best candidate
我认为何小姐是最佳人选
For my Princess Yong.
为了我的雍公主。
That's why he came.
这就是他来的原因。
That's why they asked us to bring girls of the same age.
这就是为什么他们要求我们 带同龄的女孩来。
Prince Yong will choose his wife.
雍亲王将选择他的妻子。
Prince Yong is indeed a talented , handsome man.
雍亲王确实是一位才华横溢 、英俊潇洒的男子。
The girl just returned to the capital
女孩刚回京城
You have found your perfect husband.
你已经找到了完美的丈夫。
incredible.
难以置信。
This girl is so successful!
这姑娘太成功了！
Is he kidding?
他在开玩笑吗？
Or is there something wrong with you?
或者你有什么事吗？
Your Majesty, we cannot accept his request.
陛下， 我们不能接受他的要求。
General He,
何将军，
Don't blame me for what I would say.
不要因为我会说的话而责怪我。
Wedding rings are a great strategy for our country.
结婚戒指 对我们国家来说是一项伟大的战略。
Who chooses to join the alliance is critical.
选择加入联盟的人 至关重要。
We have to think long term.
我们必须长远思考。
We must think carefully.
我们必须仔细思考。
in my opinion,
在我看来，
Ms. He didn't know how to bear such responsibility.
何小姐不知道该如何承担 这样的责任。
Prince Yong, what do you think?
雍亲王，你怎么看？
Please tell us more.
请告诉我们更多信息。
I shouldn't talk about it here.
我不应该在这里谈论它。
And I'm not a snitch.
而且我不是告密者
but something
但有件事
You need to know.
你得知道。
She learns martial arts
她学武术
He has been climbing Mount Wuhua since he was six years old.
自六岁起就登上五华山。
She came back a few months ago.
她几个月前回来了。
Since her return, she has gotten into a lot of trouble.
自从回来之后， 她就惹出了很多麻烦。
make the whole city
使得整个城市
What a mess.
一团糟。
Not to mention Thorin.
更不用说索林了。
my son
我的儿子
And there are several children of ministers here.
还有这里的几位部长的孩子。
Beaten by He Jiuling.
被贺九菱打了。
This is not true.
这个不成立。
gentlemen,
先生，
Even when you're inventing something, you have to be consistent.
即使在发明东西时，你也必须保持连贯。
how they were beaten,
他们是如何被殴打的，
why none of you
为什么你们都没有
tell me?
告诉我？
or they think
或者他们认为
Do children deserve to be beaten?
孩子们就该被打吗？
General He
何将军啊
I shouldn't talk,
我不该说话，
But it's true!
但这是真的！
Zhong Yongjun is bragging.
仲雍君在吹牛。
For example,
例如，
Just a month ago,
就在一个月前，
I have carefully cultivated grapes for several years
我精心培育了几年的葡萄
Collected by your dear daughter.
是你亲爱的女儿收集的。
Is that true?
那是真实的？
Those grapes to be sent to the palace
那些要 送到皇宫的葡萄
-Dad -it's all wasted
-爸爸 -都浪费了
- She did it all. - who knows?
- 她做到了这一切。 - 谁知道？
Mr. Li,
李先生，
I compensate you with twelve fine vines
我补偿你的十二根优质藤蔓
They must be ripe by now, right?
现在它们一定已经成熟了，对吧？
OK
好的
Master.
少爷。
So you are the one who sent the vines.
所以你就是送藤蔓的人。
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
Jiang Rong said you are not coming.
姜蓉说你不来了。
Please take a seat.
请坐。
Thank you, Your Majesty.
谢谢您，陛下。
Mr. Li,
李先生，
If you have any complaint
如果您有任何投诉
Just tell me.
就告诉我嘛。
No, nothing else.
不，没有别的。
I just remembered.
我刚想起来。
I don't mean to blame Miss He.
我并没有责怪何小姐的意思。
The vine you sent
你寄来的藤蔓
They are now bearing fruit.
现在它们都已结出果实。
I will send the grapes to the palace.
我会把葡萄送到皇宫。
Once they are ripe.
一旦它们成熟了。
I'm waiting for your grapes.
我在等你的葡萄。
Yes, Your Majesty.
是的，陛下。
Thank you Mr. Li.
谢谢李先生。
Lorde Zhongyong,
Lorde Zhongyong,
Your son is injured
你儿子受伤了
Because he insisted on fighting with Miss He.
因为他非要 和何小姐打架。
She didn't take the initiative to provoke him.
她并没有主动去招惹他。
Although my son was injured,
虽然儿子受伤了，
I have paid ten thousand taels of gold
我已经付了一万两黄金
In the name of Miss He.
以何小姐的名义。
His son decided to give up.
他的儿子决定放弃。
Still thinking?
还在想吗？
Ten thousand taels of gold?
一万两黄金？
Sim.
西姆。
As for the others you mentioned,
至于你提到的其他人，
if someone
如果有人
There are unresolved issues
有未解决的问题
Together with Miss He,
和何小姐一起，
Or that compensation
或者那个补偿
This is not enough,
这还不够，
Welcome to come to me.
欢迎来找我。
I take responsibility.
我承担责任。
No one is asking you to do this.
没有人要求你这样做。
it's all my fault.
都是我的错。
I had no idea my daughter did all this.
我不知道我女儿 做了这一切。
but
但
All this has nothing to do with Master Rong.
这一切，都 与荣爷无关。
If you encounter problems in the future,
如果以后遇到问题，
I will handle it.
包在我身上。
The responsibility is all mine.
责任全是我的。
General He,
何将军啊，
How could it have nothing to do with me?
怎么可能与我无关呢？
Miss He is my fiancé.
何小姐是我的未婚夫。
Of course I need to take care of her.
我当然需要照顾她。
What?
什么？
Miss He is Lord Rong’s fiancée?
何小姐是容大人的未婚妻？
What's wrong?
怎么了？
I have never heard that Mr. Rong is engaged.
我从来没有听说 容大人订婚了。
it's a pity.
真可惜。
How could he marry that girl from the He family?
他怎么可能娶 贺家那个姑娘？
He is not on the same level as her.
他跟她不是一个级别的。
Not a good combination.
不是一个好的组合。
completely.
完全。
Why did he say that?
他为什么要这么说呢？
Don't make a big deal out of a molehill.
别小题大做。
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
i don't even know
我什至不知道
You are engaged.
你订婚了。
General, he and my father were friends,
将军他和我父亲是朋友，
They made a deal when we were kids .
当我们还是孩子的时候，他们就达成了一项协议 。
Miss He left the capital
何小姐离开京城
I'm busy learning divination,
我正忙着 学习占卜，
no one talks about it,
没有人谈论它，
But that doesn't mean it doesn't exist
但并不代表它不存在
So Prince Yong had to find someone else.
所以雍亲王就得 另外找人了。
What do you-
你什么——
She is your fiancée.
她是你的未婚妻。
So you are not married yet.
所以你还没有结婚。
Since you are not married yet,
既然你还没有结婚，
Why can't she marry me?
她为什么不能嫁给我？
Xunnan Gan became the vassal state of Jialing.
寻南甘为 嘉陵诸侯国。
We are committed to opening up various trade routes,
我们承诺开辟各种贸易路线，
Send thousands of craftsmen,
派遣数千名工匠，
Share the West Sea and cultivate thousands of hectares of fertile land for Jialin.
共享西海，为 嘉林培育万顷良田。
We take this alliance very seriously,
我们非常重视这个联盟，
But Jialin didn't even give up on the minister's engagement.
但家麟却连大臣的订婚都没有 放弃。
Opening up trade routes can benefit both sides.
开辟贸易路线可以 使双方受益。
Your craftsmen can learn our advanced skills.
您的工匠可以学习 我们的先进技能。
Opening up the West China Sea will allow
打通西海可以让
Exchange food with Jialin.
与家琳交换食物。
This benefits both parties.
这对双方都有好处。
Why does Prince Yong think that
雍亲王为何认为
Is Jia Lin the only one who benefits?
只有家琳受益吗？
They can't show that you value this alliance.
他们无法表明 你重视这个联盟。
It's just collaboration.
这只是合作。
Moreover, if Jia Lin cancels my engagement
而且，如果家琳取消我的婚约
Xunnan became a vassal state,
寻南成为诸侯国，
It will also destroy the alliance with Xunnan
也会破坏与寻南的联盟
To obtain more benefits in the future.
为了将来获得更多的利益。
Breaking a promise is a taboo in alliances.
违背承诺是 结盟时的大忌。
Jia Lin can't do this.
家琳做不到这一点。
Prince Yong, your goal is always the highest.
雍亲王， 您的目标永远是最高的。
How could you not know?
你怎么会不知道呢？
What if I insist?
如果我坚持怎么办？
So you can try and see
所以你可以尝试看看
if you could catch my bride
如果你能抓住我的新娘
de Jialin.
de Jialin.
Mr. Rong,
荣先生，
Are you threatening me?
你在威胁我吗？
certainly.
当然。
majesty,
威严，
I am the messenger of Xunnan.
我是寻南的使者。
The only condition for forming an alliance with Jialin is marriage.
与家林结盟的唯一条件 就是联姻。
if you refuse,
如果你拒绝，
We don't need to talk anymore
我们不需要再说话了
Your Highness, please wait a moment.
殿下，请稍等。
We did not receive the order.
我们没有收到该订单。
Please give me a clear answer, Your Majesty.
请陛下 给个明确答复。
majesty.
威严。
Prince Yong, you have fallen in love with Miss He.
雍亲王， 你爱上了何小姐。
But He Jiuling is...
但贺九菱却是……
Tell Prince Yong
告诉雍亲王
You told me.
你告诉我的。
Sim.
西姆。
Prince Yong,
雍亲王，
Therefore,
正因为如此，
He even promised this girl,
甚至还向这个女孩许诺，
I can't accept it.
我无法接受。
Besides, you won’t accept it.
再说了，你也不会接受。
As for your future wife,
至于你未来的妻子，
We'll discuss that later.
我们稍后再讨论。
I think now,
我想现在，
You don't want to talk about it.
你不想谈论它。
I'll wait for your private chat.
我等你私聊。
Rong Yu.
Rong Yu.
Yes, Your Majesty.
是的，陛下。
you are engaged,
你订婚了，
But you hid it from me
但你却对我隐瞒了
Put me into an embarrassing situation.
让我陷入了 尴尬的境地。
I apologize for my mistake.
我为我的错误道歉。
I just found out today,
今天我才知道，
I will grant you and He Jiuling a marriage.
我就给你和贺九菱赐婚。
what do you think?
你怎么认为？
I thank Your Majesty on behalf of my daughter.
我代表我的女儿感谢陛下。
Even if you don't want to marry him
就算你不想嫁给他
Don't create chaos now.
现在不要制造混乱。
Thank you, Your Majesty.
感谢陛下。
Ling, let's go.
玲，走吧。
quickly.
快速地。
Go thank your Majesty.
去感谢陛下吧。
Listen, come on.
听着，快点。
He Jiuling,
He Jiuling,
A beautiful, smart, educated, dignified girl.
一个美丽聪明、 有教养、端庄的女孩。
The two must choose an auspicious day to get married.
两人必须选择 吉日结婚。
Announce it to the world, let everyone know.
向全世界宣布，让所有人都知道。
Thank you, Your Majesty.
谢谢您，陛下。
Your Highness.
殿下。
Do you know Prince Yong?
你认识雍亲王吗？
He is my senior.
他是我的前辈。
I just found out today that he is Prince Yong.
我今天才知道 他是雍亲王。
Ling,
凌,
Things have reached this point and there is no turning back.
事情已经到了这一步， 已经没有回头路了。
Just accept it.
就接受吧。
Your Majesty, you have not been in good health recently.
陛下 最近身体不太好。
This also worries me.
这也让我担心。
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Your Highness.
殿下。
Two men fight over a woman. What a show!
两个男人为了一个女人打架。 真是一场表演啊！
Excellent.
极好。
My experience with my sister was eye-opening.
我和姐姐的 经历让我大开眼界。
That's why I like women.
这就是为什么我喜欢的女人。
It's a pity that I am too young.
可惜我太年轻了。
Otherwise I will also participate in the competition
不然我也去参加比赛
Fight against Prince Yong and Duke Rong.
对抗雍亲王和荣公。
Your Highness, stop playing with me.
殿下，别玩我了。
I was serious.
我是认真的。
This is serious.
这很严重。
But Mr. Rong is a good man.
但荣先生是个好人。
I'm very happy with this agreement.
我对这个协议非常满意。
Although I can't marry you
虽然我不能嫁给你
When you have a daughter in the future
当你将来有了女儿的时候
I married her.
我娶了她。
I know from what happened today
从今天发生的事情我就知道了
The sooner you get engaged, the better.
越早订婚越好。
This is a dragon pendant given to me by my father.
这是我父亲送给我的龙吊坠。
Represent the emperor.
代表皇帝。
stand up. I'm not done yet.
起来。我还没说完。
This pendant represents the emperor.
这个吊坠代表皇帝。
With him around, no one dares to stop him anywhere.
有他在，没有人敢 在任何地方阻止他。
Acceptance as a symbol of my future wife .
接受作为我未来妻子的象征 。
My engagement is not yet confirmed.
我的订婚尚未确定。
It's too early to talk about my daughter.
现在谈论我女儿还为时过早。
I cannot accept this symbol.
我无法接受这个符号。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
I heard my father say
我听到我父亲说
maybe ten months from now
也许十个月后
Your baby is born.
你的孩子出生了。
Take it.
收下。
my future mother-in-law
我未来的婆婆
I'm going to take a nap now.
我现在要小睡一下。
As a father,
作为一名父亲，
I can't believe I didn't find out
我不敢相信我没有发现
Everything Ling has done in the capital so far.
至今凌在京城所做的一切。
I'm sorry you got involved in this.
很抱歉让你卷入这件事。
I'm happy to help you.
我很高兴为您提供帮助。
Now I feel worse.
现在我感觉更糟了。
It seems
看起来
long ago, the emperor
很久以前，皇帝
Marry Ling to Prince Yong.
将凌嫁给雍亲王。
if not you
如果不是你
Ling may have been sent to Xunnan.
凌可能已经被派往寻南了。
I will never see her again in this life.
这辈子我再也见不到她了。
General He,
何将军啊，
I'm not talking about this.
我不是在谈论这个。
I'm talking about the general.
我说的是大将军。
I have accepted this position.
我已经接受了这个职位。
I know you made a mistake
我知道你犯了一个错误
So I came to the palace to report
所以我来到皇宫通报
General He, Assistant Minister He.
何将军，何部长助理。
His Majesty summoned the two of them to the royal study.
陛下将两人召 至御书房。
As a general, you will be sent to guard Nanjiang.
作为大将军， 你将被派去镇守南江。
You must say no.
你必须拒绝。
If you don't do this,
如果你不这样做，
The He family is very powerful;
何家势力很大，
Ministers will be jealous of me.
部长们会嫉妒我的。
So the whole He family...
于是何家全家……
General He.
何将军。
Why do I feel that Ms. He is not happy?
为什么我感觉何小姐 不太高兴？
The emperor granted her a marriage. What a blessing!
皇帝赐婚给她。 多么有福啊！
Miss He loves you very much.
何小姐非常爱你。
Shouldn't she be happy?
她不应该高兴吗？
Mr. Rong, what do you think is going on?
荣先生，您认为这是怎么回事？
Mr. Rong.
荣先生。
Your Majesty, they have arrived.
陛下，他们已经到了。
- Get fired. - Yes.
- 被解雇。 - 是的。
He Liang.
He Liang.
Yes, Your Majesty.
是的，陛下。
I offended Prince Yong because of He Jiuling.
我 因为贺九龄，得罪了雍亲王。
I think even if the alliance is formed
我认为 即使联盟成立了
It must be unwilling.
一定是不情愿的。
I plan to give you an important mission
我打算交给你 一个重要的使命
and held their ground in Nanjiang
并在南江坚守阵地
Curb south-seeking.
遏制寻南。
This is a great honor for the He family
这对于何家来说是莫大的荣幸
Let us serve Jialin and His Majesty.
让我们为家林和陛下服务。
But my father is forty
但我父亲四十岁了
He is no longer the staunch warrior who fought alongside His Majesty before.
也不再是以前与陛下并肩作战的坚定战士了。
Maybe he can't bear such a big responsibility.
也许他无法承担 这么大的责任。
to alleviate His Majesty's concerns.
以减轻陛下的顾虑。
I've thought about this too.
我也想过这个问题。
Unfortunately,
很遗憾，
There is no better candidate.
没有更好的候选人了。
General Yan Zhao of the left, with a keen mind,
左将军燕昭， 心思敏锐，
He is a man of skill and strategy.
他是一个有技巧、有谋略的人。
He fought under my father for many years.
他在 我父亲手下作战多年。
I believe he can do this.
我相信他能做到这一点。
The right general Fu Rongde is good at training troops.
右将军傅荣德 善练兵
And smart and brave.
并且聪明又勇敢。
The soldiers he trained could each face three opponents.
他训练的士兵 每人可以面对三个对手。
I think he can do it too.
我想他也能做到。
He Liang, what do you think?
何亮，你觉得怎么样？
European Union...
欧洲联盟...
I think
我认为
What Chenzhou said makes sense.
郴州说得有道理。
I will think about it fondly.
我会深情地思考它。
It's all my incompetence's fault
都是我无能的错
I have betrayed His Majesty's trust.
辜负了陛下的信任。
As for the position of general,
至于大将军之位，
I hope His Majesty can recover it.
希望陛下能找回它。
I don't deserve her.
我配不上她。
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
This is the He family’s century-old battlefield loyalty
这是何家百年的 战场忠诚
This allowed the Xuanyuan family to sit on the throne.
从而让 轩辕家族坐上了皇位。
As long as the Xuanyuan family exists,
只要轩辕家族存在，
Just like the He family.
就像何家一样。
As for the position of general,
至于大将军之位，
Even if you don't go to Nanjiang, it's worth a visit.
即使你不去南江， 你也值得一去。
Moreover, only the He family
而且，只有何家
Worthy of her.
配得上她。
Thank you, Your Majesty.
谢谢您，陛下。
[Royal Library]
[皇家图书馆]
When the home
当何家
keep away
远离
Serving the country?
为国家服务？
we always
我们总是
Willing to die for the emperor.
愿意为皇帝而死。
And died for the country.
并为国家而亡。
However,
然而，
We have to be unthinking.
我们不得不思不灵。
your mother died
你母亲去世了
To save your sister.
为了拯救你的妹妹。
Your sister has been ill for six years
你姐姐病了六年
And he was treated in Wuhua Mountain for ten years.
并在五华山治疗十年。
Now,
现在，
Life finally took a turn for the better.
生活终于有了 转机。
She is getting married.
她要结婚了。
I couldn't stand it if something happened to her.
如果她出了什么事，我就无法忍受。
I don't want her involved
我不想让她参与其中
There is no risk at all.
没有丝毫的风险。
Ms. He.
何女士。
you need to be so proud
你需要如此自豪
After getting engaged to Master Rong?
和荣爷订婚后？
Can you at least be polite?
至少能有点礼貌吗？
- proudly? - It is clear.
- 自豪的？ - 很明显。
Mr. Rong's graceful manner is impressive.
荣先生举止优雅，令人印象深刻。
the best.
最好的。
Now he is with you.
现在他已经和你在一起了。
I didn't say a word in the palace.
我在宫里没有说一句话。
what did I do?
我做了什么？
Are you deaf or blind?
你是聋子还是瞎子？
Mr. Rong was right all along
荣先生一直都是对的
But you took advantage of the engagement
但你利用了订婚的机会
and spent the whole evening with him.
并和他一起度过了整个晚上。
Isn't that true?
不是这样吗？
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Stop pretending
别再假装了
Everyone knows what happened between you and Mr. Rong.
你和荣爷之间的事大家都知道了
Inside Rong Mansion.
荣府内。
looking at you.
看着你。
- who do you think You Are? - stop.
- 你以为你是谁？ - 停止。
- No one in the capital thinks - enough is enough.
- 首都没有人认为 - 够了。
You are attractive.
你很有吸引力。
Finally someone is willing to talk to you.
终于有人 愿意和你说话了。
And he even forced Master Rong to marry him.
而且还逼着荣爷娶了
Use this dirty trick.
用这个肮脏的把戏。
i know i'm scared
我知道我很害怕
Even the servants were sent away.
连仆人都打发走了。
How embarrassing!
多么尴尬！
I didn't send it.
我没有发送。
No?
没有？
Do
做
Master Rong forced him
荣爷强迫他
Spend the night with him?
和他一起过夜？
If I hadn't forced Mr. Rong
如果不是我逼容先生
sleep with you,
和你一起睡觉，
How could Duke Rong risk offending the envoy?
荣公怎么会 冒得罪使者的危险呢？
Is it responsible for you?
对你负责吗？
Do you think he really likes you?
你觉得他真的喜欢你吗？
- Keep dreaming. - let's go. let's go.
- 继续梦想。 - 我们走吧。我们走吧。
You are so shameless.
你真是无耻啊。
It also annoyed King Xunnan.
还惹恼了寻南王。
I think
我认为
You were born a bitch.
你生来就是个婊子。
Now that you know what kind of person I am,
既然你知道我是个什么样的人，
How dare you provoke me?
你怎么敢挑衅我？
Today I will teach you a lesson.
今天我就给你们上一课。
Shi Jin is very direct.
石进很直接。
Miss He, don't be angry.
何小姐，别生气。
Shijin, pare de falar.
Shijin, pare de falar.
If you dare to hurt me, my father will not let you go.
如果你敢伤害我，我父亲不会放过你。
how old are you?
你今年多大？
You should fight me.
你应该和我战斗。
Come. let's go. let's go.
来。我们走吧。我们走吧。
If you don't want to get hit, watch what you say.
如果你不想被打， 请注意你的言论。
Everyone in the capital knows it.
京城里的人都知道。
Can you shut everyone up?
你能让大家都闭嘴吗？
You did something inappropriate to Lord Rong.
你对荣大人做了不检点的事。
- Now he's angry with us. - Exactly.
- 现在他对我们很生气。 - 确切地。
enough.
足够的。
Rong Yu
Rong Yu
Ms. He,
何女士，
You took advantage of the engagement
你利用了订婚的机会
I spent the whole evening with him.
我和他一起度过了整个晚上。
Everyone knows what happened between you and Mr. Rong.
你和荣爷之间的事大家都知道了
-You have no shame. ——Rongfu.
-你没有羞耻心。 ——荣府。
I heard my father say
我听到我父亲说
Maybe, ten months later,
或许，十个月后，
Your baby is born.
你的孩子出生了。
Rong Yu!
Rong Yu!
Rong Yu, saia.
Rong Yu, saia.
Ms. He.
何女士。
Miss He, don't be rude.
何小姐，别无礼。
I need to talk to him now.
我现在需要和他谈谈。
I will defeat anyone who tries to stop me.
我会击败任何试图阻止我的人。
You caused a commotion last night.
昨晚你引起了骚动。
Say no more.
别再说了。
Zhanping,
Zhanping,
Do you remember what I said?
你还记得我说的话吗？
I remember.
我记得。
Miss He, what's wrong?
何小姐，怎么了？
Miss He, where are we going?
何小姐，我们去哪儿？
Heshan, Zhanping, don’t come with me.
鹤山、展平，别跟我来。
No need to drag me. I will go with you.
不用拖我。我和你一起去。
You follow them. I'm looking for General He.
你跟着他们。我去找何将军。
I? Is he sure?
我？他确定吗？
If Miss He bullies Mr. Rong
如果何小姐欺负容先生的话
Should I save or not?
我应该保存还是不保存？
You decide.
你决定。
Ms. He.
何女士。
Miss He, please let me go first.
何小姐，请让我先走吧。
I need a room.
我需要一个房间。
Second floor. Lotus Room.
二楼。莲花房。
Miss He...
贺小姐...
Did God send them?
是上帝派他们来的吗？
- Quickly. - Miss He.
- 迅速地。 - 何小姐。
Somewhere in between.
介于两者之间。
【Lotus Room】
【荷花房】
I asked you before
我之前问过你
If you planned to propose to the emperor, but you refused.
如果你打算向皇帝 求婚，但你拒绝了。
Don't like looking at stars?
不喜欢看星星？
Why not stay at Astrology Pavilion?
为什么不留 在占星阁？
Why did you go to the palace?
你为什么去皇宫？
Don't say you went there to eat.
别说你去那儿吃饭了。
I'm looking for General He.
我正在寻找何将军。
Do you think I would believe it?
你觉得我会相信吗？
As the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion,
作为星象阁的少主，
How dare you frame me?
你怎么敢陷害我？
Make arrangements for you?
给你安排？
Although she is not a virtuous woman,
虽然不是贤惠的女子，
Never thought I would be
从没想过我会是
The target of these rumors.
这些谣言的目标。
why did you decide
你为什么决定
take me to your home
带我去你家
Did you take off your clothes yesterday?
昨天把衣服脱了？
You misunderstood...
你理解错了...
You got it wrong.
你理解错了。
Where are the two people who just came in?
刚刚进来的两个人在哪里？
Second floor. Lotus Room.
二楼。莲花房。
- Go to Heshan. - correct.
- 去找鹤山。 - 正确的。
Who are you?
你是谁？
We don't allow three people to share a room.
我们不允许三 个人住一间房。
- This is-- - This is Mr. Rong's bag.
- 这是-- - 这是容先生的包。
This is the money the girl gave me
这是女孩给我的钱
Take all the gold. I just need this bag.
拿走所有的金子。我只需要这个包。
I feel lucky today.
我今天感觉很幸运。
He's making things up.
他在编造事情。
My brother cares about me very much.
我哥哥非常关心我。
Why doesn't he take me home?
他为什么不带我回家？
If you say your people hurt me
如果你说你的人伤害了我
How could he ignore me?
他怎么会不理我呢？
this time,
这次，
It was my fault.
是我的错。
I'll clarify this.
我会澄清这一点。
clarify? for what?
澄清？为了什么？
Who will believe you?
谁会相信你？
Rong Yu, no need to clarify.
容羽，不用澄清。
Let us be together.
让我们在一起。
Anyway, my reputation is already very bad.
反正 我的名声已经很坏了。
Don't think you can get away with it.
别以为你能逃脱惩罚。
enough.
足够的。
I'm a man.
我是一个男人。
I might lose control.
我可能会失去控制。
Do you think I have anything to lose by taking this job?
你认为我会 因为这份工作而失去什么吗？
Even if I did something to you
就算我对你做了什么
At worst, I'd be Montutus,
最坏的情况下，我会成为蒙图图斯，
Rather than being meticulous and respectful
而不是一丝不苟和尊重
Master celebrity collector.
明星收藏家大师。
The world is crueler to women
这个世界对女性更加残酷
Compared with men.
比与男人。
If you really want to put down the blade,
如果你真的想 放下刀片，
People will look down on you and hurt you.
人们会鄙视你并伤害你。
Although I want to enlighten you and protect you,
虽然我想开导你 、保护你，
I can not do anything.
我无能为力。
Did I ask you to protect me?
我有要求你保护我吗？
Why are you doing all this?
你为什么要做这一切？
Why did you give them grapes and money?
你为什么给他们葡萄和钱？
He wanted to limit me until we got married.
他想 在我们结婚之前限制我。
Rong Yu, I don’t want to marry you.
容钰，我不想嫁给你。
But you write to me every day.
但你每天都给我写信。
Said he wanted to meet under the moonlight.
说他很想在月光下见面。
I'm looking forward to our meeting.
我很期待我们的会面。
He told me he missed me and thought I was crazy.
他告诉我他想念我 并认为我疯了。
I just want to ask you out
我只是想约你出去
say clearly
说清楚
And please ask my father to cancel the engagement.
并请你去求我父亲 取消婚约。
You gave me your Turkish horse,
你把你的土耳其马给了我，
This is his favorite.
这是他最喜欢的。
My father stole something from me.
我父亲偷了我的东西。
- You even- - Rong Yu, that's enough.
- 你甚至 - - 容羽，够了。
Since I started learning martial arts,
自从我开始 学习武术，
i never thought about my husband
我从来没有想过我的丈夫
I would be a weak person like you.
我会像你一样是一个软弱的人。
You know nothing about my preferences.
你对我的喜好一无所知。
I don't know what you like.
我不知道你喜欢什么。
If we are always together,
如果我们一直在一起，
None of us will be happy.
我们谁都不会高兴。
I told you not to like me
我告诉过你不要喜欢我
I made it very clear.
我说得很清楚了。
Why don't you understand?
你为什么不明白？
He Jiuling,
He Jiuling,
I thought
我以为
It was a meaningless drunken chat.
那是一次毫无意义的醉酒聊天。
European Union -
欧洲联盟 -
- Dad - He Jiuling, what are you doing?
- 爸爸 - 何九龄，你在做什么？
You are a disgrace.
你是一个耻辱。
- You idiot. - It's not her fault. it's me.
- 你个傻冒。 - 这不是她的错。是我。
Rong Yu, get out of the way.
容宇，你让开。
I have to teach her a lesson today.
今天我得给她一个教训。
Dad, I'm sorry.
爸爸，对不起。
I didn't touch him.
我没有碰他。
Do you have any plans...
你有没有计划...
This annoys me.
这让我很恼火。
——General He. - Dad, wait. listen to me.
——何将军。 - 爸爸，等等。听我说。
Pai County,
拜县，
Let’s take Ling home first.
我们先送凌回家吧。
Mr. Rong also needs to take care of himself.
容先生也需要照顾好自己。
Don't let anyone see the mess.
不要让任何人看到乱七八糟的事情。
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
I'll be sure to give an explanation.
我一定会给出一个解释。
Come home with me quickly.
快点跟我回家吧。
let's go.
我们走吧。
Heshan,
鹤山,
Don't let anyone spread rumors.
不要让任何人传播谣言。
- Quickly. - Yes.
- 迅速地。 - 是的。
Mr. Rong, you told me
荣先生，你告诉我的
If Miss He bothers you, leave her.
如果何小姐打扰了你，就离开她吧。
I shouldn't be involved.
我不应该参与其中。
That's why I didn't go in.
这就是我没有进去的原因。
【He Mansion】
【何公馆】
Kneel down.
跪下。
Pass the baton to He Chenzhou.
接力棒，何辰洲。
Dad, do you really want to hit her?
爸爸，你真的要打她吗？
Now she actually dares to bully a man.
现在的她，竟然敢欺负一个男人。
From now on you can kill people and set fires.
以后你可以杀人 、放火。
hurry up.
快点吧。
you idiot,
你个笨蛋，
Won't you irritate me?
你不会激怒我吗？
What's this?
这是什么？
What happened, Dad?
发生什么事了，爸爸？
It's none of your business. Return to the room.
这不关你的事。返回房间。
help me.
帮我。
My father would kill me.
我父亲会杀了我。
How dare you ask for help?
你怎么敢寻求帮助？
If Rong Yu hadn’t let you go
如果容玉没有放过你
You're not going to kneel now.
你现在不会跪下。
will it be me
会是我吗
Kneel at the door of Rong Mansion.
跪在荣府门口。
Dad, the engagement has been decided.
爸爸，订婚决定了。
It's only a matter of time before this happens.
这件事只是时间问题。
it's not a big deal.
没什么大不了的。
you are mean,
你很刻薄，
How can you say that?
你怎么能这么说呢？
European Union-
欧洲联盟-
I'll finish you too
我也来结束你吧
Dad, they are really gone,
爸爸，他们真的走了，
This means Rong Yu is already with us.
这意味着容宇已经和我们在一起了。
Not what you want?
不是你想要的吗？
Don't you just want to make sure they're married?
你不是只是想确定 他们结婚了吗？
This is what you want.
这就是你想要的。
Dad, I'm sorry.
爸爸，对不起。
- I'll never do it again. - She said she would never do it again.
- 我再也不会这么做了。 - 她说她再也不会这样做了。
I will draw a clear line with Rong Yu.
我会和容羽划清界限。
I will never tease or piss you off again.
我再也不会取笑或激怒你了。
He Jiuling, you can't escape
贺九菱，你逃不掉的
This beating today.
今天的这次殴打。
your -
你的 -
group.
派。
She's sorry, Dad.
她很抱歉，爸爸。
I will beat you until you die.
我会打败你，直到你死为止。
Dad, if you hurt her,
爸爸，如果你伤害了她，
Rong Yu will cancel the wedding.
容羽将取消婚礼。
Go away.
走开。
Father, father.
父亲，父亲。
help me.
帮我。
Stop running. return!
别跑了。回来！
I want you to learn
我想让你学习
-Dad -you fool
-爸爸 -你这个傻瓜
How dare you run away?
你怎么敢逃跑？
Volt.
伏尔特。
You won't get away with this.
你不会逃脱这个惩罚。
Go away.
走开。
-Dad
-爸爸
- dad - get out
-出去
Since I started learning martial arts,
自从我开始 学习武术，
i never thought about my husband
我从来没有想过我的丈夫
It's a weakling like you.
是像你一样的弱者。
You know nothing about my preferences.
你对我的喜好一无所知。
I don't know what you like.
我不知道你喜欢什么。
If we are always together,
如果我们一直在一起，
None of us will be happy.
我们谁都不会高兴。
I told you not to like me
我告诉过你不要喜欢我
I made it very clear. Why don't you understand?
我说得很清楚了。你为什么不明白？
How should I accept your gift?
我该如何接受你的礼物？
Please get up.
请起床。
on that day,
在那一天，
I made a mistake
我犯了一个错误
Let Miss He stay in Rong Mansion.
让何小姐 留在荣府。
I'm here to apologize today.
我今天是来道歉的。
Why are you apologizing?
你为什么道歉？
If anyone is guilty, it's our fault.
如果有人有罪，那是我们的错。
Yesterday Ling was severely punished by me.
昨天玲受到了我的严厉 惩罚。
I grounded her too
我也把她禁足了
Let her reflect.
让她反思。
Isn’t it a bit harsh?
是不是有点严酷了？
my Lord.
我的主。
Rong Yu is a member of this family.
容宇是这个家庭的一员。
bell tower.
钟楼。
Miss He can't leave,
何小姐不能走，
She is in a bad mood
她心情不好
and refused to eat.
并拒绝进食。
what do I do?
我该怎么办？
For a warrior, missing a few meals is not a problem at all.
对于一个武者来说， 少吃几顿饭根本不是问题。
But what...
但什么...
Don't bother me with these things anymore.
别再用这些事情来烦我了。
You can leave now.
你现在可以离开了。
Sim.
西姆。
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
I'm not just doing this for you.
我这么做不只是为了你。
I also taught my daughter.
我也教育过我的女儿。
Stop begging.
别再乞讨了。
For my troubled daughter.
为了我陷入困境的女儿。
♫ Under the sunset♫
♫ 黄昏的夕阳下 ♫
♫I traveled thousands of miles♫
♫我旅行千里之外♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 月光下演奏西塔琴 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 饮料不会让我忘记 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫我写给你的渴望♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 无法逃脱命运♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫回首我看到你在等待♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫我们的生活充满 欢乐和悲伤♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 欲望结晶 成闪亮的星系♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 你默默转身 ，合上结婚簿♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫问天上有多少颗星星♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫我写给你的渴望♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 无法逃脱命运♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫回首我看到你在等待♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫我们的生活充满 欢乐和悲伤♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 欲望结晶 成闪亮的星系♫
♫I play the sitar softly waiting for someone like you♫
♫我轻轻地弹奏西塔琴 等待像你这样的人♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫最终你 是我不可避免的命运♫